[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "You spoke to Tameka tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Yes, I did speak with her tonight and she did tell me that her son was OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tameka"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "POS", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Where was this snake and how did it get out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, from what I've read and from what information that's out currently is that the snake escaped it's enclosure, which was housed in the pet store in the first floor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Is that what we believe the cause of death is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, you know, that would be the cause of death involving a snake, especially of that size.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Could that have attracted the snake, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "People getting messages on their cell phones and so on to try and encourage them to see if they can see these two kids, Hanna Anderson and Ethan Anderson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Piers, it's extremely helpful, these Amber alerts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hanna Anderson", "Ethan Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Is there a sensible way of spending public money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, the first thing -- one of the first things you learn in law school, Piers, any person that defends himself has a fool for a client.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "MD", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "But what about the rights -- what about the rights, Star, of the victims that he shot who he may now have the legal right to interrogate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Not may, does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "CC", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "How can that be right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Because the criminal justice system is there where the defendant is innocent, unless and until proven guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Even when he's admitted I'm the shooter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "But admission of responsibility for the act is not admission of culpability under the law.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Do you mind if I say, this is legal gooblededoo?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "ONES: I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "So it's a necessary evil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "It is a necessary evil.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I wish I could say I'm surprised.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Have you experienced it in New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Not as much because New York is sort of my city, and I tend to go places where I'm expected.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "So you're almost subliminally avoiding it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Have you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Absolutely, in the middle of the street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "And how do you reach when you hear that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "I act like they're not talking to me because it's not what they call you, it's what you answer to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Has it gotten any better since the first black president of the United States or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Yes, it's not so much that it's gotten better.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "You know, the people whoever were in the Madison Avenue store when they saw Oprah Winfrey, they immediately thought black woman can't afford this so why am I letting her in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RB", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah Winfrey"], "LOCATION": ["Madison Avenue"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What do you think of Oprah linking the Emmett Till case to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Clearly, the facts and circumstances were very much different but in terms of it being pivotal and starting a discussion, and starting a turn, I think she's exactly right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Emmett Till"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "You think he's innocent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "No, it's not that I think he's innocent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "-- did he actually say it's not true?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "If you get told today that they no longer want you here at CNN, I guarantee you, you going to ask them to go through the process.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Tell me not to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I will tell you, please shut up and let me do the talking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Why are you starting with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Does it matter what people are like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Well, first of all, I don't know what is wrong with the way Hillary looks now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "I'm curious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I invited her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "You know when -- when folks leave the White House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "Syria"]}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What do you think about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I think it's a very dangerous thing and not just in Libya but also in Syria.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "He -- he gets Benghazi and I get boobies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Benghazi guy go to guy for the boobies.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Does it matter, Josh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I mean, look, the first amendment applies to all Americans including students in schools.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Now, that's real family entertainment, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "The point that I make is that goddamnit, I do think that you glorify on public television homosexuality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Graham"]}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What is your -- your personal reaction to the fact that the Graham family that you served under for so long have finally sold out now to, you know, a -- a dot-com billionaire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, first great sadness given the contribution of the Graham family to journalism, to the national good health in terms of promoting a kind of reporting that serves everybody in this country, and a kind of honesty and a kind of principled management.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Graham"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Where is the line to be drawn between what the guardians say and Glenn Greenwald and on behalf of Snowden have been doing and where the public interest lies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Look, it's always a tough call.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn Greenwald", "Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Did you see it by any chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I saw it in an -- in an early cut.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "But did your view of Nixon -- has it changed over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nixon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Do you think we're (ph) forgiving (ph) of him with history?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", "VBG", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "No, I'm more empathy to his demons, I would say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", ":", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "How are you dealing with all the attention that comes with the fact you may be the first ever NFL official, female?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "You know, Piers, what -- well, when I get to thinking about this, I've never worked a preseason where there's been more focus on the next season.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "I mean, what's it like when you get out there with these honking (ph) guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", ":", "NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "They're professionals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VB", "RB", "VB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Are they going to go to the football, want to instinctively shout at the referee for some terrible call and discover it's their mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Well, I always tell them if I'm coaching them or being a mom to them, that don't ever be in a game whenever you're playing or sitting back watching and let the official make one play that you think blew the game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Have you had some surprising messages of support and goodwill from people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Yes, I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 704, "question": "You nervous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "No...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "What do you make of A-Rod, that little cheat down the road at the Yankees?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "I really don't have any comments on that, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "Do you have a favorite team -- a favorite NFL team?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}}]